AIDAN JONES

Projects & Portfolio - linktr.ee/aidcaljone **Email-** aijo1282@colorado.edu

Profile

Currently attending CU Boulder as a strategic communication major, I am following the media design track while minoring in Creative Technology Design (CTD). I have gained experience in art direction, visual identity, and web development throughout my time at CU. This skill set has enabled me to work with local brands to develop their brand identity and expand my portfolio as a photographer, videographer, and designer.

Awards & Merit

2022

Rotary Club International Scholarship Media design promotes peace

2019

CMCI Pathways to Excellence
College of Media Information & Communication
Summer Intensive scholarship

2018

Dedication to Graphic Design Award Awarded by Dr. Claudia Lastella

Education

University of Colorado Boulder
B.A. in Strategic Communication
Diploma expected 2023
GPA: 3.83
Relevant Coursework
Design Foundations, Visual Design,
Story Design, Concept Design

Monarch High School Louisville, CO 2016-2019 (GPA: 3.6) Relevant Coursework Digital Art & Design, Videography

Experience

2021 - Present HINDSIGHT

Art Director | hindsightjournal2020.com

Hindsight is a student-run creative nonfiction journal at the University of Colorado Boulder, publishing undergraduate personal essays, new journalism, memoirs, portraits, artwork, and more. The main goal of art direction is deciding what art to include in the journal and where it goes in collaboration with digital production. Outside of the journal, art direction concentrates on designing marketing materials and maintaining the overall look and feel of Hindsight as a brand.

<u>2021 - Present</u> ROAM Boulder

Creative Director | roamboulder.com

ROAM Magazine is CU Boulder's first life and style publication. ROAM provides quality insight on Fashion, Lifestyle, Culture, and Art. The creative director guides all projects and is responsible for the overall quality of work produced by the creative cohort.

<u>2017 - Present</u> Freelance

Freelance Graphic Design

After taking digital art & design in my first year of high school, I quickly wanted to work with actual clients to make their visions come to life. Teachers, friends, and family took notice of my graphic design skills and requested media such as logo designs, posters, album cover art, web graphics, and any design-related needs. Every project I took on has expanded my portfolio while giving me client-based experience.